迎着风
Brace the wind.
陛下  光之王已经履行了承诺
The lord of light has made good on his promise, my king.
他的火焰已将冰雪消融
His fires have melted the snows away.
前路畅通无阻
The way ahead is clear.
我们进军临冬城
We ride for Winterfell.
您将一举夺下它
And you will take it.
光之王让我看到波顿的旗帜熊熊燃烧
The lord has shown me Bolton Banners burning.
您将得到本应属于您的东西
You will receive what is yours by right.
陛下
Your grace.
准备行军
Prepare to form up.
陛下
Your grace.
讲
Tell me.
士卒  黎明前逃走了很多
The men, many deserted before dawn.
有多少
How many?
将近半数
Nearly half.
所有佣兵和全部的马匹
All the sellswords with all the horses.
陛下
Your grace.
尽管说  总不会比兵变更糟
Speak up. Can't be worse than mutiny.
把她放下来
Cut her down.
陛下
Your grace.
有人看到梅莉珊卓女士骑马出了营地
The lady Melisandre was just seen riding out of camp.
传令集合  准备行军
Get the men into marching formation.
向临冬城进发
On to Winterfell.
他双手一扬
He raised his hands
它们一下子都站了起来
and they all stood up at once.
成千上万  世界上最庞大的军队
Tens of thousands of them. The biggest army in the world.
你打算怎么做
So what are you gonna do?
我打算祈祷它们别学会爬长城
I'm gonna hope they don't learn how to climb the Wall.
但是龙晶...
But the dragonglass...
没人拿得回来了
No one's ever getting that back now.
反正也是杯水车薪
It wouldn't have mattered anyway.
除非我们有座龙晶山
Not unless we had a mountain of it.
可你杀死了一个异鬼
But you killed a white walker.
用的是长爪
With Longclaw.
我眼见钢斧在他们面前如玻璃般粉碎
I saw them shatter steel axes like they were glass.
-可长爪...  -是瓦雷利亚钢
- But Longclaw... - is Valyrian steel.
七国上下还有多少把瓦雷利亚钢剑
How many Valyrian steel swords are left in the Seven Kingdoms?
远远不够
Not enough.
有史以来第一个牺牲誓言兄弟性命
The first Lord Commander in history to sacrifice
去救野人的总司令
the lives of sworn brothers to save the lives of wildlings.
跟黑城堡最遭憎恨的人做朋友感觉如何
How's it feel to be friends with the most hated man in Castle Black?
我刚到这儿你就是我朋友了
You were friends with me when I first came here.
那时候可没什么人喜欢我
And I wasn't winning any elections back then.
那么这一杯敬我们
Here's to us, then.
但凭他们嘲笑吧
Long may they sneer.
怎么了
What?
我想求你一件事
I wanted to ask you something.
求你为我做件事
To ask something of you.
送我  吉莉和孩子去旧镇
Send me, Gilly, and the baby to Oldtown
让我受训成为学士
so I can become a maester.
那才是我天生该做的事  不是打仗
That's what I'm meant to be. Not this.
这里需要你  山姆
I need you here, Sam.
要是你走了  还有谁能给我可信的忠告
If you leave, who's left to give me advice I trust?
还有艾迪啊
Well, there's Edd.
我成为学士对你更有用
I'd be more use to you as a maester.
对大家都更有用  伊蒙学士不在了
More use to everyone now that Maester Aemon is gone.
学城有世界上最大的图书馆
The Citadel has the world's greatest library.
我会学习历史
I'll learn about history,
策略  医术
strategy, healing.
还有其他知识
And other things,
到时候用得上的
things that will help when--
那些东西来的时候
when they come.
如果吉莉留在这里  她会死的
If Gilly stays here, then she'll die.
她以我的名字命名的孩子也会死
And the baby that she named after me will die.
我也会死  为了保护他们
And I'll end up dying, too, trying to protect them.
那样的话  我在世上最后所见
Which means that the last thing that I'll see in this world
将是我没能保护他们时她的眼神
will be the look in her eyes when I fail them.
我宁愿面对一千异鬼  也不愿见到那一幕
And I'd rather see a thousand white walkers than see that.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你知道学城也会让你发誓不近女色
You know that the Citadel will make you swear off women, too.
他们可以试啊
Oh, they'll bloody try.
-山姆  -怎么啦
- Sam. - What?
山姆
Sam.
你那时刚被打了个半死  你是怎么...
You had just been beaten half to death. How did you--
小心翼翼呗
Oh, very carefully.
真高兴在末日劫难之时还有人交了好运
I'm glad the end of the world's working out well for someone.
我会回来的
I'll come back.
敬你归来
To your return.
敬我归来
To my return.
这边
Aye, this way.
小姐
My lady!
史坦尼斯
Stannis.
史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩来了  带着军队
Stannis Baratheon is coming. His whole army.
你怎么知道是史坦尼斯
How do you know it's Stannis?
他们举着烈焰红心旗
They're carrying his flaming heart banners.
我在黑水河上见过  一辈子也忘不了
From the Blackwater. I'll never forget it.
在这里挖战壕
Trench here.
距城墙三百码再挖一道
Another one 300 yards from the castle wall.
让他们快点儿
Hurry them along.
在两坡之间挖
Dig between those two rises.
-传令下去  -我跟你走
- Spread out. - I'm with you.
-弓箭手  -传令下去
- Archers! - Spread out!
马上派人出去征收粮草
And send out a foraging party immediately.
日出开始围攻
Siege begins at sunrise.
不会有围攻了  陛下
There's not going to be a siege, Your Grace.
我们毫无胜算
We've got no chance!
不要  求你
No, please, please.
波顿还找了女人替他打仗
Bolton has women fighting for him?
我不为波顿家效命
I don't fight for the Boltons.
我是塔斯的布蕾妮
I'm Brienne of Tarth.
我本是蓝礼·拜拉席恩的彩虹护卫
I was kingsguard to Renly Baratheon.
那个有你容貌的影子刺杀他时  我也在场
I was there when he was murdered by a shadow with your face.
你使用血魔法杀了他吗
You murdered him with blood magic?
是的
I did.
以蓝礼·拜拉席恩一世
In the name of Renly of house Baratheon, first of his name,
安达尔人和先民的真王
rightful king of the Andals and the First Men,
七国的统治者暨全境守护之名
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms and protector of the realm,
我  塔斯的布蕾妮  判你死刑
I, Brienne of Tarth, sentence you to die.
你可有遗言
Do you have any last words?
来吧  履行你的职责
Go on, do your duty.
看来我们的活儿干完了
Looks like we're done here.
我投降  我投降
I surrender! I surrender!
我接受你的投降
And I accept your surrender.
我们回去吧
Let's head back.
我妻子一定孤单了
My wife must be lonely.
夫人
My lady.
我来送您回房间去
I've come to escort you back to your chamber.
跟她走吧  拜托
Go with her, please.
我知道拉姆斯的本性
I know what Ramsay is.
我知道他会怎么待我
I know what he'll do to me.
如果注定要死
If I'm going to die,
就让我趁还没完全失却本心前死掉
let it happen while there's still some of me left.
死
Die?
谁说你要死了
Who said anything about dying?
你不能死
You can't die.
你父亲是北境守护
Your father was Warden of the North.
拉姆斯需要你
Ramsay needs you.
不过他应该不需要完整的你
Though I suppose he doesn't need all of you.
只需要为他生育子嗣的那些部分
Just the parts he'll use to make his heir,
等你生了一两个儿子  就没有使用价值了
until you've given him a boy or two and he's finished using them.
然后怎么处置那些部分  他自有好点子呢
Then he's got incredible plans for those parts.
所以  我们是等他回来
So, shall we wait for him to come back
还是这就开始
or should we begin now?
你要我决定吗
You're leaving it to me?
太好了
Good.
我们开始吧
Let's begin.
臭佬  住手
Reek... stop!
住手
Stop!
打开大门
Open the gate!
他回来了
He's coming back.
看来我有的忙活了
I can see I have my work cut out for me.
你俩  出去
You two, out.
你是我名单上的第一个
You were the first person on my list, you know.
你杀了西利欧·佛瑞尔  记得他吗
For killing Syrio Forel. Remember him?
很可能不记得了
Probably not.
还有其他几个人
I've gotten a few of the others.
千面之神偷走了几个
The many-faced god stole a few more from me.
但他把你留给我  我很高兴
But I'm glad he left me you.
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
我听不到
I can't hear you.
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
我是艾莉亚·史塔克
I'm Arya Stark.
你知道你是谁吗
Do you know who you are?
你是无名之辈
You're no one.
你什么也不是
You're nothing.
女孩夺走了一条命
A girl has taken a life.
不该夺的命
The wrong life.
我说对了
I was right about her.
是啊
You were.
你还没准备好
You're not ready.
根本没准备好
Not at all.
那人的命不该由你取
That man's life was not yours to take.
女孩偷了千面之神的东西
A girl stole from the many-faced god.
如今债已欠下
Now a debt is owed.
只有死亡能还人命债
Only death can pay for life.
不要
No! No!
不要  你不能死  别死啊
No, you... don't die! Don't die!
你为什么要哭
Why are you crying?
他是我朋友
He was my friend.
不  他不是  你没听他说什么吗
No, he wasn't. Didn't you listen to him?
他是无名之辈
He was no one.
可如果你是...
But if you're...
这是谁
Who's this?
无名之辈
No one at all.
女孩也该做无名之辈
Just as a girl should have been
才能拿走大厅里的脸
before she took a face from the hall.
脸是给无名之辈的
The faces are for no one.
而你仍是有名之人
You are still someone.
对于有名之人
And to someone,
脸与毒药无异
the faces are as good as poison.
我看不到了
I can't see.
怎么回事
What's happening?
What's happening?!
-祝你返乡顺利  -谢谢
- I wish you a safe journey home. - Thank you.
原谅我  孩子
Forgive me, child.
我衷心祝你幸福快乐
I wish you all the happiness in the world.
或许我改日会来看你
Maybe I'll come visit you sometime.
或许我会去看你
Maybe I'll come visit you.
别等太久
Don't wait too long.
家里还有个贵妇人等着我娶
Got a noblewoman to marry back home.
你想要个清白的姑娘
You want a good girl,
但也缺不了坏坏的小婊子
but you need the bad pussy.
准备好了就出发  大人
Whenever you're ready, my lord.
别再把它弄丢了
Try not to lose it this time.
我再也不会取下来了
I'll never take it off again.
我知道你并不希望离开多恩
I know you didn't want to leave Dorne,
但我很高兴你能回家
but I'm glad you're coming home.
你母亲迫切地想要见你
Your mother's desperate to see you.
很高兴崔斯丹与我们同行
I'm glad Trystane is coming with us.
他看上去是个好小子
He seems like a nice boy.
你很幸运
You're lucky.
指定的婚姻很少能...
Arranged marriages are rarely so--
指得这么好
so well arranged.
你觉得母亲会喜欢他吗
Do you think mother will like him?
只要她看到你幸福  我相信她会的
If she sees you're happy, I'm sure she will.
你真的这么想
You really believe that?
你想想  除了她的孩子们
Have you ever known your mother to like anyone
你母亲还喜欢过谁
aside from her children?
她喜欢你
She likes you.
这我可不敢肯定
I'm not so sure about that.
听着
Listen...
我想告诉你一件事
There's something I wanted to tell you.
很久以前就应该告诉你了
Something I should have told you long ago.
怎么说呢
So...
既然你如今的阅历也广了些
Now that you've seen more of the world,
想必也知道世事有多复杂
you've learned how complicated things can be,
人心有多难测
people can be.
兰尼斯特家和马泰尔家多年来相互仇视
The Lannisters and the Martells have hated each other for years,
但你却与崔斯丹坠入爱河
but you've fallen in love with Trystane.
这是机缘巧合  真的  这可能性多小啊
It was an accident, really. I mean, what were the chances?
你碰巧爱上了那个
You happen to fall in love with the man
指给你的男人
you were assigned to marry?
我想说的是...
My point is...
我们无法选择自己所爱的人
We don't choose whom we love.
这只是...
It just, well--
我们不能自持
It's beyond our control.
-我真像个傻瓜  -不  没有的事
- I sound like an idiot. - No, you don't.
我想说的是...我想表达
What I'm trying to say-- what I'm trying
却又难以启齿的是...
and failing to say--
我知道你想说什么
I know what you're trying to say.
不  恐怕你不懂
No, I'm afraid you don't.
我懂
I do.
我都知道
I know.
你和母亲的事
About you and mother.
我想我内心深处早就知道了
I think a part of me always knew.
并且  我很庆幸
And I'm glad.
我很庆幸你是我的父亲
I'm glad that you're my father.
弥赛菈
Myrcella?
弥赛菈  弥赛菈
Myrcella? Myrcella?
你们爱她  不是吗
You love her, don't you?
怎么能不爱她
How could you not?
当然你们的爱都是无望的
Of course it's hopeless for the both of you.
一个是斗技场的佣兵  一个是不名誉的骑士
A sellsword from the fighting pits, a disgraced knight.
谁都不适合成为女王的好夫君
Neither one of you is fit consort for a queen.
但我们谁没有奢求一份错位的爱情呢
But we always want the wrong woman.
他总是这么喜欢废话吗
Does he always talk so much?
安达尔人乔拉
Jorah the Andal.
灰虫子
Torgo Nudho.
他不该在这儿
He should not be here.
没错  但他就在这儿
No, but he is.
女王已下令将他逐出城外
Our queen ordered him exiled from city.
若不是有他  女王就死了
Our queen would be dead if not for him.
真的  而我  如果不是这个...
小个子
侏儒
应该是这个词
不好意思
我的瓦雷利亚语有点森苏
有点生疏
生疏  谢谢你
Punila. Thank you.
我很遗憾
I am sorry.
当时我不在场  不能为女王而战
Sorry I not there to fight for our queen.
你错过了一场精彩的斗殴
You missed a good scrap.
这些都不重要了
None of that matters now.
我们在这儿自怨自艾
The longer we sit here bantering,
丹妮莉丝还困在蛮荒之地遭罪
the longer Daenerys is out there in the wilderness.
他说的没错  龙飞向北边
He's right. The dragon headed north.
如果我们要找她  就得往北走
If we're going to find her, that's where we'll have to go.
"我们"
We?
你是兰尼斯特
You're a Lannister.
女王力求推翻你们家族的统治
The queen intends to remove your family from power.
而我要助她得偿所愿
And I intend to help her do it.
你来这儿才几天
You've been here for how many days now?
我为她而战已有多年
I've fought for her for years.
最早的时候她不比孩子大多少
Since she was little more than a child.
-你背叛过她  -说话小心点
- You betrayed her. - Careful now.
她放逐了你  两次  如果我没记错的话
And she exiled you. Twice, I believe.
第二次还是多亏了你呢
The second time thanks to you.
别把你犯下的罪行归咎到我头上  莫尔蒙
Don't blame me for your crimes, Mormont.
他说的对  女王放逐了乔拉
He's right. Our queen exiled Jorah.
但他说的也没错  乔拉救过她的命
And he's right. Jorah saved her life.
或许女王对他的看法已经有所改变了
Perhaps she feels differently about him now.
或许不然  但我们要问过她才会知道
Perhaps not. The only way we'll know is if we ask her.
好吧  或许他可以跟我们一起
Fine, fine. I suppose he can join us.
只要他答应别趁我睡觉时杀了我就行
Just as long as he promises not to kill me in my sleep.
如果我要杀你  你的眼睛一定睁着
If I ever kill you, your eyes will be wide open.
恕我直言  我们为何要带上你
Forgive me, but why would we bring you?
-什么  -你在野外追踪过野兽吗
- Pardon me? - Have you ever tracked animals in the wilderness?
那倒没有  但我还有别的实用技能
Not precisely, but I have other skills that would be useful.
你能战斗吗
Can you fight?
我战斗过
I have fought.
我没有自称是伟大的战士
I don't claim to be a great warrior.
你骑术如何
Are you good on a horse?
马马虎虎
Middling.
所以你基本上只会耍嘴皮子
So mainly you talk.
还会喝酒  我都活这么久了
And drink. I've survived so far.
我对此深为佩服  但这次远征要你无用
Which I respect, but you would not help us on this expedition.
你留在弥林却可以帮助我们
You would help us here in Meereen, though.
我们都没有治理城邦的经验
None of us have experience governing a city
除了他
except for him.
你不是想向女王证明自己的价值吗
You want to prove your value to the queen?
就在弥林证明吧
Prove it right here in Meereen.
他是个连当地语言都说不利索的异邦侏儒
He's a foreign dwarf that barely speaks the language.
弥林人凭什么听他的
Why would the Meereenese listen to him?
他们不听他的
They wouldn't.
他们会听灰虫子的
They will listen to Grey Worm.
我要和你们同去
I'll come with you.
我要找到女王
I'll find our queen.
-你的身体状况还不能出行  -我可以
- You are not strong enough to go anywhere. - I am.
他可以  他是我见过的最有种的阉人
He is. He's the toughest man with no balls I ever met.
可你还是不能去
But you still can't go.
这里的人民信任你
The people believe in you.
他们知道你是女王的代言人
They know you speak for the queen.
没错
It's true.
只有无垢者能维持弥林的和平
Only the unsullied can keep the peace in Meereen.
如果你离开
If you leave,
弥林肯定一分为二  自相残杀
half this city will consume the other half.
还有弥桑黛
And Missandei.
女王最信任的人是弥桑黛
Our queen trusts no one more than Missandei.
肯定不是我
Certainly not me.
女王最亲近的密友
The queen's closest confidante,
无垢者的指挥官
the commander of the unsullied,
以及来自异邦的疤脸侏儒
and a foreign dwarf with a scarred face.
祝你们好运  我的朋友们
Good fortune, my friends.
弥林古老而荣耀
Meereen is ancient and glorious.
尽量别毁了她
Try not to ruin her.
看来只有你我二人了  安达尔人乔拉
Looks like it's you and me, Jorah the Andal.
我们去找几匹好马
Let's find some good horses.
路上还有说不完的话呢
We have so much to talk about.
你好啊  老朋友
Hello, old friend.
我还以为我们在一起很快乐
I thought we were so happy together
结果你抛弃了我
until you abandoned me.
我猜没必要问你是怎么找到我的
I suppose there's no point asking how you found me.
西边的鸟儿会唱歌  东边的鸟儿也会唱
The birds sing in the west, the birds sing in the east,
只要你懂得如何聆听
if one knows how to listen.
听说你已经获得了龙之母的垂青
They tell me you've already found favor with the mother of dragons.
怎么说呢  她没有处决我
Well, she didn't execute me,
算是开了个好头
so that's a promising start.
现在英雄们去找她了
Now the heroes are off to find her
而我困守在此
and I'm stuck here
意欲挽救本城于内战边缘
trying to placate a city on the brink of civil war.
老朋友有什么建议给我吗
Any advice for an old comrade?
情报是关键
Information is the key.
你需要了解敌人的优势和策略
You need to learn your enemy's strengths and strategies.
你需要知晓哪位朋友笑里藏刀
You need to learn which of your friends are not your friends.
但愿我认识一个触角无所不至的能人
If only I knew someone with a vast network of spies.
但愿如此
If only.
一座雄伟的古城
A grand old city
因暴力  腐败和欺骗而濒临崩溃
choking on violence, corruption, and deceit.
谁有经验驯服
Who could possibly have any experience
如此巨大而蠢笨的野兽呢
managing such a massive, ungainly beast?
我真心想念你
I did miss you.
噢  我知道
Oh, I know.
我们必须回家
We have to go home.
可怜又可爱的孩子
Oh, my poor, sweet thing.
疼吗
Does it hurt?
我们必须回家
We have to go home.
卓耿
Drogon.
你能带我回弥林吗
Can you take me back to Meereen?
你带我飞了多远
How far did you carry me?
卓耿  我们得回去
Drogon, we need to return.
我的人民需要我
My people need me.
这里没有食物
Well, there's no food.
你至少给我们捕些晚饭回来啊
At the very least, you could hunt us some supper.
忏悔
Confess.
我有罪
I have sinned.
我现在知道了
I see that now.
我怎会糊涂那么久
How can I have been so blind for so long?
我想清洁自己
I want to be clean again.
我想获得赦免
I want absolution.
老妪高举金灯来到我面前
The Crone came to me with her lamp raised high.
让沐浴圣光的...
And by its holy light--
您想忏悔
You wish to make a confession?
我忏悔之后  能否放了我
Once I've confessed, will I be free?
对陛下的处置将视陛下的罪行而定
Your grace will be dealt with according to her sins.
那么愿圣母慈悲
The Mother have mercy, then.
我忏悔  我在婚外出轨
I lay with a man outside the bonds of marriage. I confess.
跟谁
Name him.
蓝赛尔·兰尼斯特
Lancel Lannister.
您的堂弟  国王的侍从
Your cousin and the king's squire.
-我那时孤单害怕  -您有丈夫
- I was lonely and afraid. - You had a husband.
一个成天狎妓的丈夫...
A husband off whoring every chance he--
他的罪无法抵消您的罪
His sins do not pardon your own.
愿诸神宽恕我
May the gods forgive me.
其他男人呢
Other men?
没有了
No.
没有别人了吗
No others?
没有了
No.
在诸神面前撒谎可是大罪
Speaking falsehoods before the gods is a great crime.
您明白吧
You understand this?
明白
I do.
有人说您的孩子
There are those that say your children
并非您与劳勃国王所生
were not fathered by King Robert,
而是通奸乱伦的孽种
that they are bastards born of incest and adultery.
谎言
A lie.
史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩的无耻谎言
A lie from the lips of Stannis Baratheon.
他妄图篡夺铁王座
He wants the throne,
但他哥哥的孩子阻碍他即位
but his brother's children stand in his way.
所以他污蔑他们是野种
So he claims they are not his brother's.
那个混蛋
That filth.
根本就是一派胡言
There is not one shred of truth to it.
我否认
I deny it.
很好
Good.
但这些罪名极为严重
But these are terrible charges.
七国子民必须知道真相
And the realm must know the truth of them.
若陛下所言非虚
If Your Grace has given honest testimony,
审判必将还您清白
your trial will prove your innocence.
审判  我已经忏悔了
Trial? I have confessed.
只是其中一项罪名
To a single sin.
其余的您都否认了
Others you have denied.
审判将辨明真伪
Your trial will separate the truths from the falsehoods.
谨遵总主教大人的英明裁断
I bow to the wisdom of your high holiness.
但我可否请求
But if I might beg
圣母稍示慈悲
for just one drop of the Mother's Mercy.
我都不知多久
I haven't seen my son--
没见过我的儿子了
I don't know how long it's been.
我要见见他  求您了
I need to see him, please.
您已踏出了回归正途的第一步
You have taken the first step on the path back to righteousness.
有鉴于此
In light of this,
我允许您回到红堡
I will permit you to return to the Red Keep.
谢谢您
Thank you.
圣母慈悲
The Mother is merciful.
您应当感谢她
It is her you should thank.
我会的  我会的
I will. I will.
我发誓  我必将日夜感激
I swear it, day and night.
很好
Good.
我可以走了吗
Am I free to go?
待你赎罪之后
After your atonement.
赎罪
My atonement?
诸位面前之罪人
A sinner comes before you.
是兰尼斯特家的瑟曦
Cersei of House Lannister.
托曼国王陛下的生母
Mother to His Grace King Tommen.
劳勃国王陛下的遗孀
Widow of His Grace King Robert.
她承认犯下欺骗和乱伦的大罪
She has committed the acts of falsehood and fornication.
罪人业已忏悔
She has confessed her sins
并祈求宽恕
and begged for forgiveness.
为表示悔改
To demonstrate her repentance,
罪人愿意弃去一切自尊与伪装
she will cast aside all pride, all artifice,
将诸神创造她的原本模样
and present herself as the gods made her
示与你等
to you,
全城的善男信女
The good people of the city.
罪人携庄严诚恳之心意而来
She comes before you with a solemn heart,
袒露胸怀
shorn of secrets,
在诸神与世人面前赤裸身体
naked before the eyes of gods and men...
踏上赎罪之旅
to make her walk of atonement.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
耻辱
Shame.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
耻辱
Shame.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
耻辱
Shame.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
shame. Shame.
耻辱
Shame.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
耻辱
Shame.
-骚屄  -耻辱
- Cunt! - Shame.
婊子
Whore!
-耻辱  -婊子
- Shame. - Whore!
耻辱
Shame.
-婊子  -婊子
- Whore! - Whore!
耻辱
Shame.
-婊子  -罪人
- Whore! - Sinner!
-耻辱  -荡妇  姐弟通奸
- Shame. - Bitch! Brother fucker!
-婊子  -耻辱
- Whore! - Shame.
-滚开  -耻辱
- Fuck off! - Shame.
耻辱
Shame.
王家奶头万岁  你这个荡妇
All hail the royal tits. You're a bitch!
耻辱
Shame.
-打她  -婊子
- Get her! - Whore!
-荡妇  -通奸
- Bitch! - Fucker!
-通奸  -荡妇
- Fucker! - You bitch!
-耻辱  -骚屄
- Shame. - Cunt!
耻辱
Shame.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
-姐弟通奸  -荡妇
- Brother fucker! - Bitch!
我玩过的鸡巴只有太后玩过的一半多
I've had half as many cocks as the queen.
-荡妇  -耻辱
- Bitch! - Shame.
-耻辱  -罪人  -婊子  -淫妇
- Shame. - Sinner! - Whore! - Slut!
耻辱
shame.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
婊子  婊子  婊子
Whore! Whore, whore.
我是兰尼斯特  舔我啊
I'm a Lannister. Suck me off!
-来舔我  荡妇  -退后
- Suck me off, you bitch! - Back!
-婊子  -耻辱
- Whore! - Shame.
耻辱
shame.
婊子
Whore!
婊子  婊子  婊子
Whore! Whore! Whore!
耻辱  耻辱
shame. Shame.
耻辱
Shame.
shame.
耻辱
Shame.
-荡妇  荡妇  -耻辱
- Bitch! Bitch! - Shame.
姐弟通奸
Brother fucker!
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
耻辱
shame.
-婊子  -姐弟通奸
- Whore! - Brother fucker!
-婊子  -耻辱
- Whore! - Shame.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
耻辱
shame.
Shame.
耻辱
shame.
-耻辱  -通奸
- Shame. - Fucker!
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
耻辱
shame.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
shame. Shame.
耻辱
Shame.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
耻辱
Shame.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
耻辱
Shame.
耻辱  耻辱
Shame. Shame.
耻辱
Shame.
陛下
Your grace.
您能回来真是太好了
It's good to have you back.
来
Come.
我们送您进去
We'll take you inside.
我需要检查一下您的脚
I need to have a look at those feet.
我可有荣幸
May I have the honor of
向您介绍御林铁卫的新成员
presenting the newest member of the kingsguard?
陛下明鉴  他发下了神圣的静默誓言
If it please your grace, he has taken a holy vow of silence.
他发誓  在杀掉陛下所有敌人
He has sworn that he will not speak
将罪恶驱离王国以前
until all his grace's enemies are dead
决不开口
and evil has been driven from the realm.
是谁来帮你  是史坦尼斯
Who came to your aid? Stannis.
现在他需要你
Now he needs you.
我们人手不足  无法扭转局势
We don't have enough men to make any difference.
野人们能扭转局势
The wildlings will make a difference.
野人们绝不会为史坦尼斯效命
The wildlings will never fight for Stannis.
-我告诉过他  -你救了他们的小命
- I told him before. - You saved their bloody lives.
如果他们打算住在七国之内
If they're gonna live in the Seven Kingdoms,
受我们的长城保护  他们就该自己争取
safe behind our Wall, they ought to fight for the damn place.
-这不是他们的战争  -开门
- It's not their fight. - Open the gates!
史坦尼斯呢
Stannis?
希琳公主呢
Shireen? The princess?
总司令大人
Lord Commander.
您带回来的一个野人
It's one of the wildlings you brought back.
说他知道您叔叔班扬
Says he knows your uncle Benjen.
说他还活着
Says he's still alive.
你确定他说的就是班扬
Are you sure he's talking about Benjen?
他说那人是首席游骑兵
Said he was first ranger.
说他知道去哪里找到那人
Said he knows where to find him.
有人说看到你叔叔上个满月在艰难屯
Man says he saw your uncle at Hardhome at the last full moon.
-可能说谎  -有可能
- Could be lying. - Could be.
有办法找出真相
There are ways to find out.
-他人呢  -那边
- Where is he? - Over there.
叛徒
为了守夜人
For the watch.
for the watch.
奥利
Olly...
为了守夜人
For the watch.
本字幕首发于字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
翻译  草草 送小孩 潇湘月影
翻译  Silmar 白月 泰斯
校对  Silmar 泰斯  顾问  屈畅(ccxx)
时间轴  崽猪 加森 全家筒 aaaBao
后期 吉吉  总监 泰斯·雪诺
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
改编自《冰与火之歌》
原著 乔治·R·R·马丁
权力的游戏
第五季 第十集